Irving Berlin Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Correspondence (Box 297-376)
  - General correspondence
    - Miller, Gilbert and Kitty, 1950-1962 (Box-folder 346/28)
    - Miller, Mitch, 1958-1962 (Box-folder 346/29)
    - Miller, William J., 1978 (Box-folder 346/30)
    - Milligan, Mary, 1948 (Box-folder 346/31)
    - Mills, E.C., 1942-1957 (Box-folder 346/32)
    - Minneapolis Auditorium, 1944-1956 (Box-folder 346/33)
    - Minnelli, Liza, 1965-1974 (Box-folder 346/34)
    - Miss America Pageant, 1956 (Box-folder 346/35)
    - Mitgang, Herbert, 1964-1988 (Box-folder 346/36)
    - Mitler, Milton, 1978-1987 (Box-folder 346/37)
    - Mok, Michel, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 346/38)
    - Montgomery, Elizabeth, 1950-1955, undated (Box-folder 346/39)
    - Moon, Joseph F., 1949-1962 (Box-folder 346/40)
    - Moore, Dorothy K., 1950 (Box-folder 346/41)
    - Morath, Max, 1969-1986 (Box-folder 346/42)
    - Morehouse, Ward, 1943-1985 (Box-folder 346/43)
    - Moreno, Dorothea E., 1950 (Box-folder 346/44)
    - Morgan, Junius S., 1942 (Box-folder 346/45)
    - Morgan and Brother Manhattan Storage Co., Inc., 1969-1988, undated (Box-folder 346/46)
    - Morgan Guaranty Trust Company, 1965-1992 (Box-folder 346/47)
    - Morganthau, Henry, 1941-1943 (Box-folder 346/48)
    - Moses, Ann Mary Robertson (Grandma Moses), 1955-1988 (Box-folder 346/49)
    - Moses, Robert, 1945-1981 (Box-folder 347/1)
    - Motion Picture Relief Fund, 1943 (Box-folder 347/2)
    - Mount Sinai School of Medicine, 1964-1975 (Box-folder 347/3)
    - Moynihan, Daniel P., 1982-1989 (Box-folder 347/4)
    - Mundy, Ethel, 1954-1970 (Box-folder 347/5)
    - Mundy, Finy and William, 1942-1951 (Box-folder 347/6)
    - Mundy, Mary, 1958-1961 (Box-folder 347/7)
    - Muni, Paul, 1955 (Box-folder 347/8)
    - Murphy, Justice Frank, 1942-1947 (Box-folder 347/9)
    - Murphy, George, 1963-1968 (Box-folder 347/10)
    - Murray, Thomas Edward, 1948-1978 (Box-folder 347/11)
    - Murrow, Edward R., 1952 (Box-folder 347/12)
    - Museum of Broadcasting, 1989 (Box-folder 347/13)
    - Museum of Fine Arts (Boston), 1969 (Box-folder 347/14)
    - Music Corporation of America, 1948-1954 (Box-folder 347/15)
    - Music Dealers Service, Inc., 1958-1959 (Box-folder 347/16)
    - Music Publishers' Protective Association, 1929-1964 (Box-folder 347/17)
    - Music Operators of America, 1957 (Box-folder 347/18)
    - Music Publishers' Association of the United States, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 347/19)
    - Music Publishers' Contact Employees, 1942-1958 (Box-folder 347/20)
    - Myers, Lester C., 1957 (Box-folder 347/21)
    - "M" miscellaneous
      - M-Marg (Box-folder 347/22)
      - Mari-Mazz (Box-folder 347/23)
      - McA-McF (Box-folder 348/1)
      - McG-McW (Box-folder 348/2)
      - Me (Box-folder 348/3)
      - Mi (Box-folder 348/4)
      - Mo-Mt (Box-folder 348/5)
      - Mu (Box-folder 348/6)
    - "M" unidentified (Box-folder 348/7)
    - NBC, 1939-1962 (Box-folder 349/1)
    - Nagrin, Daniel, 1946-1988 (Box-folder 349/2)
    - Nash, Ogden, 1950 (Box-folder 349/3)
    - Nathan, Casper, 1954 (Box-folder 349/4)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1945 (Box-folder 349/5)
    - National Citizen's Council on Civil Rights, 1949 (Box-folder 349/6)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1949-1988 (Box-folder 349/7)
    - National Committee for the Universal Copyright Convention, 1954 (Box-folder 349/8)
    - National Council of American Soviet Friendship, 1943 (Box-folder 349/9)
    - National Council on Crime and Delinquency, 1967 (Box-folder 349/10)
    - National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis (March of Dimes), 1942-1981 (Box-folder 349/11)
    - National Jewish Center for Immunology, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 349/12)
    - National Jewish Hospital, 1958-1985 (Box-folder 349/13)
    - National Jewish Ledger, 1942 (Box-folder 349/14)
    - National Music Awards, 1976 (Box-folder 349/15)
    - National Music Publishers' Association, 1970-1987, undated (Box-folder 349/16)
    - National Park Service, 1949 (Box-folder 349/17)
    - National Society of the Daughters of the American Revolution, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 349/18)
    - National Sojourners, Inc., 1979 (Box-folder 349/19)
    - National Variety Artists, 1952-1962 (Box-folder 349/20)
    - Negro Actors Guild of America, 1950-1968 (Box-folder 349/21)
    - Navy Department, 1947 (Box-folder 349/22)
    - Navy Relief Society, 1942-1946 (Box-folder 349/23)
    - Neilson, Rutgers, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 349/24)
    - Nelson, Boris Erich, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 349/25)
    - Nelson, Eddie, 1946-1966 (Box-folder 349/26)
    - New Dramatists Committee, 1952-1986 (Box-folder 349/27)
    - New York City, 1944-1973 (Box-folder 349/28)
    - New York Magazine, 1975-1981 (Box-folder 349/29)
    - New York Post, 1939 (Box-folder 349/30)
    - New York Public Library, 1949-1986 (Box-folder 349/31)
    - New York University, 1946, 1982 (Box-folder 349/32)
    - New York Times, 1949-1986 (Box-folder 349/33)
    - Newman, Phil, 1942-1949 (Box-folder 349/34)
    - Nicholson and Galloway Roofing and Waterproofing, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 349/35)
    - Niebuhr, Reinhold, 1950 (Box-folder 349/36)
    - Nielsen, Poul Overgaard, 1950 (Box-folder 349/37)
    - Night of Stars, 1942-1961 (Box-folder 349/38)
    - Niklad, Roberta Anne, 1958 (Box-folder 349/39)
    - Nimitz, Chester, 1945 (Box-folder 349/40)
    - Nixon, President Richard M., 1954-1988, undated (Box-folder 349/41)
    - Nizer, Louis, 1948-1967 (Box-folder 349/42)
    - North, John Ringling and Henry, 1942-1947 (Box-folder 349/43)
    - Norworth, Jack, 1949-1957 (Box-folder 349/44)
    - Novak, Robert, 1942-1951 (Box-folder 349/45)
    - Novins, Louis A., 1947-1949 (Box-folder 349/46)
    - "N" miscellaneous
      - Na (Box-folder 350/1)
      - Ne (Box-folder 350/2)
      - Ni-Ny (Box-folder 350/3)
    - Oberstein, Eli E., 1943-1948 (Box-folder 350/4)
    - O'Brien, Jack, 1962-1985, undated (Box-folder 350/5)
    - O'Connor, Cardinal John J., 1984-1988 (Box-folder 350/6)
    - O'Connor, Walter, 1963-1980 (Box-folder 350/7)
    - O'Conor, Herbert, 1942 (Box-folder 350/8)
    - Office of War Information, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 350/9)
    - O'Hara, John, 1954-1962 (Box-folder 350/10)
    - Oldfield, Barney, 1960-1980 (Box-folder 350/11)
    - Orange County, Calif., 1972 (Box-folder 350/12)
    - Oshman, Robert, 1965-1971, undated (Box-folder 350/13)
    - "O" miscellaneous
      - Oaa-Ocaz (Box-folder 350/14)
      - Oda-Omz (Box-folder 350/15)
      - Ona-Orz (Box-folder 350/16)
      - Osa-Ozz (Box-folder 350/17)
    - Paar, Jack, 1957-1962 (Box-folder 351/1)
    - Page, Geraldine, 1983 (Box-folder 351/2)
    - Page, Ruth, 1942-1977 (Box-folder 351/3)
    - Paley, William S., 1942-1978 (Box-folder 351/4)
    - Palmer, Philip E., 1962-1984 (Box-folder 351/5)
    - Pan, Hermes, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 351/6)
    - Paramount Pictures Corp.
      - 1941-1945 (Box-folder 351/7)
      - 1946-1953, 1985 (Box-folder 351/8)
    - Parish, Romola, 1942 (Box-folder 351/9)
    - Park Jr., H. Halsted, 1946, undated (Box-folder 351/10)
    - Parks, Lee, 1956-1987, undated (Box-folder 351/11)
    - Parnell, Val, 1949-1951 (Box-folder 351/12)
    - Parsons, Louella, 1951-1954 (Box-folder 351/13)
    - Parker, Dorothy, 1945 (Box-folder 351/14)
    - Patterson, Richard C., 1954-1955 (Box-folder 351/15)
    - Pearson, Drew, 1942-1950 (Box-folder 351/16)
    - Pease and Ellman, Inc., 1941-1946 (Box-folder 351/17)
    - Peck, Gregory, 1971-1983 (Box-folder 351/18)
    - Pell, Isabel, 1948-1950 (Box-folder 351/19)
    - Pemberton, Brock and Mrs., 1943 (Box-folder 351/20)
    - Peters, Bernadette, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 351/21)
    - Peters, Roderic, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 351/22)
    - Philadelphia Inquirer, 1953-1963 (Box-folder 351/23)
    - Phipps, Howard and Harriet, 1962-1984 (Box-folder 351/24)
    - Pickford, Mary, 1948 (Box-folder 351/25)
    - Pierpont Morgan Library, 1977 (Box-folder 351/26)
    - Pitts, Zazu, 1943 (Box-folder 351/27)
    - Porter, Cole, 1933-1985, undated (Box-folder 351/28)
    - Powell, Bruce, 1942-1949 (Box-folder 351/29)
    - Power, Tyrone, 1942-1950 (Box-folder 351/30)
    - Precht, Robert, 1968-1974, undated (Box-folder 351/31)
    - Preminger, Otto, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 351/32)
    - Price, Vincent, 1975 (Box-folder 351/33)
    - Prince, Harold, 1977-1984 (Box-folder 351/34)
    - Princeton University, 1985 (Box-folder 351/35)
    - Prinzmetal, Myron, 1948-1962, undated (Box-folder 351/36)
    - "P" miscellaneous
      - Paa-Paq (Box-folder 351/37)
      - Par-Paz (Box-folder 351/38)
      - Pe-Pf (Box-folder 352/1)
      - Ph-Pl (Box-folder 352/2)
      - Po-Pz (Box-folder 352/3)
    - Quayle, Anthony, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 352/4)
    - Quigley Publications, 1938-1955 (Box-folder 352/5)
    - "Q" miscellaneous (Box-folder 352/6)
    - Radio City Music Hall, 1982 (Box-folder 352/7)
    - Radio Free Europe, 1960 (Box-folder 352/8)
    - Rand, Robert, 1942 (Box-folder 352/9)
    - Rankin, A.H., 1941-1947, undated (Box-folder 352/10)
    - Rasaf, Andy, 1954-1958, undated (Box-folder 352/11)
    - RCA, 1944-1980 (Box-folder 352/12)
    - Reader's Digest, 1944-1985 (Box-folder 352/13)
    - Reagan, Ronald
      - 1980-1984 (Box-folder 353/1)
      - 1985-1989 (Box-folder 353/2)
    - Redfield, Catherine, 1942 (Box-folder 353/3)
    - Reform Jewish Appeal, 1962-1981 (Box-folder 353/4)
    - Reiner, Gabriel, 1956 (Box-folder 353/5)
    - Reinhart, Marie Louise, 1973-1986 (Box-folder 353/6)
    - Reinheimer, Howard E.
      - 1936-1942 (Box-folder 353/7)
      - 1943-1948 (Box-folder 353/8)
      - 1949-1968 (Box-folder 353/9)
    - Reis, Arthur M., 1947-1951 (Box-folder 353/10)
    - Remick, Lee, 1965 (Box-folder 353/11)
    - Reuben, Arnold, 1949-1962, undated (Box-folder 353/12)
    - Reynolds, Debbie, 1957-1983, undated (Box-folder 353/13)
    - Rice, Andy, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 353/14)
    - Richman, Harry, 1958-1963 (Box-folder 353/15)
    - Richmond, Larry, 1942-1943, 1954 (Box-folder 353/16)
    - Richmond, Maurice, 1942-1948 (Box-folder 353/17)
    - Rickenbacker, Eddie, 1952 (Box-folder 353/18)
    - Rindler, Milton, 1967-1984 (Box-folder 353/19)
    - Riskin, Robert, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 353/20)
    - Ritter, Murray, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 353/21)
    - Rivera, Diego, 1948 (Box-folder 353/22)
    - RKO Radio Pictures, 1937-1943 (Box-folder 353/23)
    - Robbins, Jack, 1944-1949 (Box-folder 353/24)
    - Robbins, Jerome, 1949-1989, undated (Box-folder 353/25)
    - Robertson, Cary, 1944 (Box-folder 353/26)
    - Robertson, Cordella B., 1942-1949 (Box-folder 353/27)
    - Robinson, Sophie, 1963-1985, undated (Box-folder 353/28)
    - Rockefeller, David, 1951 (Box-folder 354/1)
    - Rockefeller, Jr., David, 1972 (Box-folder 354/2)
    - Rockefeller, III, John D., 1966 (Box-folder 354/3)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1952-1965 (Box-folder 354/4)
    - Rockefeller, Winthrop, 1950-1970 (Box-folder 354/5)
    - Rodgers, Richard, 1946-1952, 1976-1979, 1989 (Box-folder 354/6)
    - Rodgers, Richard and Oscar Hammerstein II, 1946-1960 (Box-folder 354/7)
    - Rodgers and Hammerstein Organization, 1987 (Box-folder 354/8)
    - Roffman, Richard H., 1942-1943 (Box-folder 354/9)
    - Rogers, Ginger, 1960 (Box-folder 354/10)
    - Rogers, William P., 1971 (Box-folder 354/11)
    - Romberg, Sigmund, 1942-1951 (Box-folder 354/12)
    - Rome, Harold, 1952-1971 (Box-folder 354/13)
    - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1942-1946 (Box-folder 354/14)
    - Roosevelt, Jr., Eleanor B., 1946-1956 (Box-folder 354/15)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, 1941-1944, undated (Box-folder 354/16)
    - Roosevelt, Kermit, 1941-1955 (Box-folder 354/17)
    - Roosevelt, Quentin and Frances, 1943-1987 (Box-folder 354/18)
    - Roosevelt, Brig. General Theodore, 1942 (Box-folder 354/19)
    - Roquiere, Georges, 1965-1978 (Box-folder 354/20)
    - Rose, Billy, 1945-1946, undated (Box-folder 354/21)
    - Rosenstock, Milton, 1949-1983 (Box-folder 354/22)
    - Rosenthal, Helen, 1943-1945 (Box-folder 354/23)
    - Rosenwald, William, 1946-1949 (Box-folder 354/24)
    - Roudenko, Luba, 1950-1951, undated (Box-folder 354/25)
    - Royal, John F., 1944-1950 (Box-folder 354/26)
    - Royal Society, 1967-1975 (Box-folder 354/27)
    - Rubinstein (Gourielli) Helena, 1956 (Box-folder 354/28)
    - Rubin, J. Robert, 1948-1952 (Box-folder 354/29)
    - Ruby, Harry
      - 1937-1942 (Box-folder 354/30)
      - 1943-1959 (Box-folder 354/31)
      - 1960-1967 (Box-folder 354/32)
      - 1968-1971 (Box-folder 354/33)
      - 1972-1974, undated (Box-folder 354/34)
    - Rudolph Wurlitzer Company, 1942 (Box-folder 354/35)
    - Rumsey, John W., 1947-1960 (Box-folder 354/36)
    - Runyon, Damon and Mrs., 1942 (Box-folder 354/37)
    - Ryskind, Morrie, 1968-1978, undated (Box-folder 354/38)
    - "R" miscellaneous
      - Ra (Box-folder 354/39)
      - Re-Rh (Box-folder 355/1)
      - Ri (Box-folder 355/2)
      - Roa-Ror (Box-folder 355/3)
      - Ros (Box-folder 355/4)
      - Rot-Ry (Box-folder 355/5)
    - "R" unidentified (Box-folder 355/6)
    - S.A.C.E.M.
      - 1948-1958 (Box-folder 356/1)
      - 1954-1988, undated (Box-folder 356/2)
    - Sacks, Emanuel (Manie), 1942-1957 (Box-folder 356/3)
    - Safier, Gloria, 1948-1961, undated (Box-folder 356/4)
    - Salabert, Inc., 1946-1953 (Box-folder 356/5)
    - Salute to France, 1955 (Box-folder 356/6)
    - Samrock, Victor, 1949-1950, undated (Box-folder 356/7)
    - Samuel, Aimee V., 1946 (Box-folder 356/8)
    - Sanders, Harland, 1970 (Box-folder 356/9)
    - Sandrich, Mark, 1938-1968 (Box-folder 356/10)
    - Snag, Philip, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 356/11)
    - Santly, Lester, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 356/12)
    - Saranoff, Julius, 1950-1967 (Box-folder 356/13)
    - Sardi, Vincent, 1962-1971 (Box-folder 356/14)
    - Sarnoff, David, 1954-1971 (Box-folder 356/15)
    - Schary, Dore, 1958-1968 (Box-folder 356/16)
    - Schenck, Joseph, 1927-1953 (Box-folder 356/17)
    - Schenk, Nicholas M., 1942-1969 (Box-folder 356/18)
    - Schine, Myer and Hildegarde, 1968-1988 (Box-folder 356/19)
    - Schlaifer, Charles, 1949-1984 (Box-folder 356/20)
    - Schneider, Hilda, 1948-1973 (Box-folder 356/21)
    - Schuman, William, 1952-1963 (Box-folder 356/22)
    - Schuster, M. Lincoln, 1943-1966 (Box-folder 356/23)
    - Schwartz, Arthur, 1923-1982, undated (Box-folder 356/24)
    - Schwartz, Jean, 1946, undated (Box-folder 356/25)
    - Schwerdtfeger, Otto M., M.D. see Dear Doctor
    - Scouts, Boy and Girl, 1940-1989 (Box-folder 357/1)
    - Seeger, Pete, 1974 (Box-folder 357/2)
    - Seldes, Gilbert, 1942-1947, undated (Box-folder 357/3)
    - Selznick, David O., 1942-1950 (Box-folder 357/4)
    - Shalit, Gene, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 357/5)
    - Shamir, Yitzhak, 1988 (Box-folder 357/6)
    - Shapiro, Elliot, 1942-1951 (Box-folder 357/7)
    - Sharett, Moshe, 1952 (Box-folder 357/8)
    - Shaw, Arnold, 1950-1988 (Box-folder 357/9)
    - Shaw, Ray, 1943-1970 (Box-folder 357/10)
    - Shaw, Sam, 1949-1970, undated (Box-folder 357/11)
    - Shawnee Press
      - 1952-1965 (Box-folder 357/12)
      - 1966-1973 (Box-folder 357/13)
      - 1974-1984 (Box-folder 357/14)
    - Shearer, Norma, 1953 (Box-folder 357/15)
    - Sheldon, Sidney, 1948-1988 (Box-folder 357/16)
    - Sherman, Allan, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 357/17)
    - Sherwood, Robert, 1942-1986, undated (Box-folder 357/18)
    - Shields, Brooke, 1983 (Box-folder 357/19)
    - Shinko Music Publishing Co., Ltd., 1963-1965 (Box-folder 357/20)
    - Shipler, Guy Emery, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 357/21)
    - Shor, Toots, 1942 (Box-folder 357/22)
    - Shore, Dinah, 1949-1976, undated (Box-folder 357/23)
    - Short, Hassard (Bobbie), 1942-1956, undated (Box-folder 357/24)
    - Show (magazine), 1963 (Box-folder 357/25)
    - Shubert, J.J., 1949-1955 (Box-folder 357/26)
    - Shubert, John, 1962 (Box-folder 357/27)
    - Shubert, Lee and Mrs., 1942-1953 (Box-folder 357/28)
    - Shubert, Milton, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 357/29)
    - Shubert, Theater Corp., 1954 (Box-folder 357/30)
    - Shumlin, Herman, 1948-1964 (Box-folder 357/31)
    - Shurr, Louis, 1942-1968, undated (Box-folder 357/32)
    - Siegal, Sol, 1943-1973 (Box-folder 357/33)
    - Sillman, Leonard, 1947-1949 (Box-folder 357/34)
    - Sills, (Greenough) Beverly, undated (Box-folder 357/35)
    - Silvera, Albert and Olga, 1951-1955 (Box-folder 357/36)
    - Silverman, Fred, 1978 (Box-folder 357/37)
    - Simon, Harry
      - 1963-1975, undated (Box-folder 357/38)
      - 1942-1958 (Box-folder 357/39)
    - Simon, Louis, 1942-1958 (Box-folder 358/1)
    - Simon and Schuster, 1942-1967 (Box-folder 358/2)
    - Simpson, Sid, 1944 (Box-folder 358/3)
    - Sinatra, Frank and Mrs., 1947-1980 (Box-folder 358/4)
    - Sinatra (Lambert), Nancy, 1984 (Box-folder 358/5)
    - Sinclair, Upton, 1942 (Box-folder 358/6)
    - Skala, Lilia, 1953-1966 (Box-folder 358/7)
    - Skouras, Charles, 1947-1960 (Box-folder 358/8)
    - Small, Paul, 1949 (Box-folder 358/9)
    - Smith, Henry, 1946 (Box-folder 358/10)
    - Smith, Kate, 1945-1969 (Box-folder 358/11)
    - Smith, Oliver, 1949-1962 (Box-folder 358/12)
    - Smithsonian Institution, 1966-1975 (Box-folder 358/13)
    - Smythe, Edward James, 1940 (Box-folder 358/14)
    - Snyder, Ted, 1936-1949, undated (Box-folder 358/15)
    - Sobel, Louis, 1947-1970 (Box-folder 358/16)
    - Society for the New York Hospital, 1951-1958 (Box-folder 358/17)
    - Society for the Preservation & Encouragement of Barbershop Quartet Singing in America, 1959-1978 (Box-folder 358/18)
    - Sohmer, Harry J., 1950-1964 (Box-folder 358/19)
    - Solotaire, George, 1956-1963 (Box-folder 358/20)
    - Sonderson, Lora, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 358/21)
    - Sondheim, Stephen, 1966-1978 (Box-folder 358/22)
    - Re: Song Folio 1 Order Forms and Letters, 1945 (Box-folder 358/23)
    - Songwriters Guild of America, 1942 (Box-folder 358/24)
    - Songwriters Hall of Fame
      - 1969-1978 (Box-folder 358/25)
      - 1979-1993, undated (Box-folder 358/26)
    - Songwriters of America, 1953, undated (Box-folder 358/27)
    - Songwriters' Protective Association, 1937-1958, undated (Box-folder 358/28)
    - Sosenko, Anna, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 358/29)
    - Southeast Missouri State College, 1969 (Box-folder 358/30)
    - Spaatz, Carl, 1950 (Box-folder 358/31)
    - Spaeth, Sigmund, 1942-1962 (Box-folder 358/32)
    - Sparkman, John, 1953-1976 (Box-folder 358/33)
    - Spellman, Cardinal Francis, 1947-1967 (Box-folder 358/34)
    - Stafford, Jo, 1948-1950 (Box-folder 358/35)
    - Stamats, Herbert, 1952-1962 (Box-folder 358/36)
    - Stanley, Aileen, 1949-1955 (Box-folder 358/37)
    - Starr, Benjamin, 1942 (Box-folder 358/38)
    - Stassen, Harold, 1955 (Box-folder 358/39)
    - State Department, United States, 1948-1951 (Box-folder 358/40)
    - Steinway and Sons, 1945 (Box-folder 358/41)
    - Stern, Isaac, 1985 (Box-folder 358/42)
    - Stern, J. David, 1941-1949, undated (Box-folder 358/43)
    - Stettinius, Edward R., 1942-1948 (Box-folder 358/44)
    - Stevens, Mr. and Mrs. Ashton, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 359/1)
    - Stevenson, Adlai, 1952-1961 (Box-folder 359/2)
    - Stewart, Charles, 1950-1966 (Box-folder 359/3)
    - Stewart, James, 1944 (Box-folder 359/4)
    - Stewart, James (Jimmie), 1989 (Box-folder 359/5)
    - Stoddard, Hud, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 359/6)
    - Stokowski, Leopold, 1969 (Box-folder 359/7)
    - Stone, Norman, 1970-1987 (Box-folder 359/8)
    - Stoner, Mickey, 1978-1984 (Box-folder 359/9)
    - Stork Club, 1950-1978 (Box-folder 359/10)
    - Stout, Rex, 1942-1949 (Box-folder 359/11)
    - Streisand, Barbra, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 359/12)
    - Stuart, Lyle, 1947-1973 (Box-folder 359/13)
    - Styne, Jule, 1949-1985 (Box-folder 359/14)
    - Sullivan, Ed, 1942-1973, undated (Box-folder 359/15)
    - Sullivan, J. Branigan, 1962-1968 (Box-folder 359/16)
    - Sulzberger, Iphigene Ochs, 1949-1988 (Box-folder 359/17)
    - Susskind, David, 1983 (Box-folder 359/18)
    - Swayze, John Cameron, 1954 (Box-folder 359/19)
    - Sweet Adelines, Inc.
      - 1971-1972 (Box-folder 359/20)
      - 1973-1986 (Box-folder 359/21)
    - Sweetland, Thelma Van Winkle, 1949-1956 (Box-folder 359/22)
    - Swope, Herbert B.
      - 1939-1946 (Box-folder 359/23)
      - 1946-1970 (Box-folder 359/24)
    - Swordack, Mallie, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 359/25)
    - Sydow, Jack, 1966 (Box-folder 359/26)
    - Sylvester, Robert, 1956-1970 (Box-folder 359/27)
    - Symington, Stuart, 1950 (Box-folder 359/28)
    - "S" miscellaneous
      - S-Sa (Box-folder 360/1)
      - Sca-Scho (Box-folder 360/2)
      - Schr-Scz (Box-folder 360/3)
      - Se-Sf (Box-folder 360/4)
      - Sg-Sh (Box-folder 360/5)
      - Si-Sl (Box-folder 361/1)
      - Sm-So (Box-folder 361/2)
      - Sp-Sta (Box-folder 361/3)
      - Ste-Sty (Box-folder 361/4)
      - Su-Sz (Box-folder 361/5)
    - Taft, Walbridge S., 1931-1949 (Box-folder 362/1)
    - Talcott, J. Frederick, 1940 (Box-folder 362/2)
    - Tannen, Nat, 1942-1944 (Box-folder 362/3)
    - Taps, Jonie, 1946-1962 (Box-folder 362/4)
    - Tashjian, M.J., 1940-1950 (Box-folder 362/5)
    - Taubert, Rudolph, 1964-1971 (Box-folder 362/6)
    - Taylor, Davis, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 362/7)
    - Taylor, Deems, 1942-1944 (Box-folder 362/8)
    - Taylor, Elizabeth, 1961 (Box-folder 362/9)
    - Telephone Hour, 1962 (Box-folder 362/10)
    - Temple University, 1954-1965 (Box-folder 362/11)
    - Tenant, Ira, 1941-1944, undated (Box-folder 362/12)
    - Tenberge, Jacobus, 1948-1981 (Box-folder 362/13)
    - Tengstrom, Hikka S., 1982-1985 (Box-folder 362/14)
    - Tepper, Saul, 1968-1980 (Box-folder 362/15)
    - Theater Development Fund, 1971-1988 (Box-folder 362/16)
    - Theodore Roosevelt Association, 1950-1986 (Box-folder 362/17)
    - Theodore Rooseelt Centennial Commission, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 362/18)
    - Thiele, Bob, 1953-1959 (Box-folder 362/19)
    - Thomas, David, 1953-1977 (Box-folder 362/20)
    - Thomas, Lowell, 1942-1952 (Box-folder 362/21)
    - Thompson, Charles W., 1955-1961 (Box-folder 362/22)
    - Thompson, Gordon V., 1942-1945, 1952 (Box-folder 362/23)
    - Tibbett, Lawrence and Mrs., 1940-1946 (Box-folder 362/24)
    - Time, Inc., 1942-1985 (Box-folder 362/25)
    - Tiomkin, Dmitri, 1956-1975 (Box-folder 362/26)
    - Tobias, Charles, 1956-1970, undated (Box-folder 362/27)
    - Tobias, Harry, 1945-1987, undated (Box-folder 362/28)
    - Todd, Michael, 1942-1950 (Box-folder 362/29)
    - Toland, John, 1975 (Box-folder 362/30)
    - Tomerlin, Lysle, 1945-1947 (Box-folder 362/31)
    - Tours, Elliott, Frank Jr. and John, 1977-1988 (Box-folder 362/32)
    - Tours, Frank and Helen, 1940-1970, undated (Box-folder 362/33)
    - Town Hall, Inc., 1946-1976 (Box-folder 362/34)
    - Town & Country Magazine, 1967 (Box-folder 362/35)
    - Treasury Department, United States, 1947-1955 (Box-folder 362/36)
    - Treible, William, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 362/37)
    - Truman, Harry, 1945-1963 (Box-folder 362/38)
    - Truman, Margaret, 1951 (Box-folder 362/39)
    - Tuchman, Lester, 1979, undated (Box-folder 362/40)
    - Tucker, Sophie, 1940-1962, undated (Box-folder 362/41)
    - Tunney, Gene, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 362/42)
    - Turtle Bay Tree Fund, 1970-1988 (Box-folder 362/43)
    - TV Guide, 1972 (Box-folder 362/44)
    - TWA, 1953 (Box-folder 362/45)
    - The Twentieth Century, 1962 (Box-folder 362/46)
    - 20th Century Fox
      - 1938-1949 (Box-folder 362/47)
      - 1950-1954 (Box-folder 363/1)
      - 1955-1980, undated (Box-folder 363/2)
    - Tyng, Lucien H., 1941 (Box-folder 363/3)
    - "T" miscellaneous
      - T-Te (Box-folder 363/4)
      - Th-Tj (Box-folder 363/5)
      - To-Ty (Box-folder 363/6)
    - Uggams, Leslie, 1964 (Box-folder 364/1)
    - Ungar, Arthur, 1940-1949 (Box-folder 364/2)
    - Ungerleide and Co., 1938 (Box-folder 364/3)
    - Union of Dutch Music Publishers and Dealers, 1969 (Box-folder 364/4)